weddingchaos.co.uk 2005-02-06

# Wedding Chaos - plan your wedding, venues, photographers, cakes, caterer, wedding dresses, we have help for it all!

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting your right to privacy. Wedding Chaos respects your privacy and we will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you provide to us remains private. Information provided will only be stored on computers based in the UK.

We collect only the minimal personal information required for maintaining data with regards to the transactions of the Wedding Chaos web site.

Wedding Chaos is the sole owner of the personal information collected from this web site and any data collected will be used solely for managing our business and in order to provide a better service to our customers.

For control of our business, we collect IP addresses, which is the automatic number assigned to your computer when you surf the web. The IP address allows us to count total number of "hits" on our sites. However, your IP address is not connected to any personally identifiable or on-line contact information like a name and address, so you remain anonymous.

We may need to disclose your data to appropriate persons where required by law.

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware Wedding Chaos is not responsible for the privacy policy of other web sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

If we decide to change our privacy policy we will post any changes to this web site.

Wedding Chaos reserves the right to change this statement at any time.
